Mingying(Justin) LIN

Mingyingl233@gmail.com

(+61) 435107511

Melbourne, VIC

Portfolio: www.mingyingl.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mydev/

SKILLS:

HTML & CSS3 & Sass

UI/UX Design

React.js & Next.js

Redux

Typescript

Javascript/ES6/ES7

RESTful APIs & GraphQL

Bootstrap & Chakra & MUI

WordPress

Responsive design

Node JS & Nest JS

MongoDB & MySQL

Jira, Slack, Docker, Git

Express JS

Adobe CC Suite

Figma & Sketch

EDUCATION:

07/2018 - 12/2020

The University of Melbourne Master of Information Technology (IT)

 Specialisation in Human–Computing Interaction

06/2015 - 07/2018

RMIT University Bachelor of Information Technology (IT)

• Major in Computing

SUMMARY:

Self-motivated Full-stack developer with human-computer interaction and computing background and experience of web UI/UX design and development. Equally effective researching and working as a dynamic team member. Fast learner who can quickly grasp and apply new ideas.

EXPERIENCE:

Unicent

Web Developer 01/2022 - 11/2022

- Consulted & Performed UI/UX design and Front-end development for all client projects.
- Designed modern business websites with Prototying tools, with 98% client satisfaction.
- Improved existing WordPress websites' usability and add new features.

Freelance

UI/UX Designer 01/2021 - 12/2021

- Collaborated with the team and to launch a B2C mini-program on social media.
- Developed and managed 20+ websites for small business using WordPress.

Mangotech Group

UI/UX Designer Intern 10/2020 - 01/2021

- Solved customer needs and business challenges through User Research, Wireframing and Prototying.
- Collaborated with product managers and engineers to help define requirements and road map.
- Analysed and tested the website and provide solutions that meet measurable requirements and goals.

PROJECTS:

Jungle Meet 09/2022 - 11/2022 UI/UX Designer/ Full-stack Developer

- · Designed and produced relevant elements and styles guideline for the website and modified them based on the feedback.
- · Collaborated with other engineers and contributed 30+ upgrade and bug fix pull requests.
- · Analysed and tested the website and provide possible solutions that meet measurable targets.